foreign
let's get straight to our top 10 list of
stocks that we're tracking we welcome
our team as well today and let's start
off with the big deal that was announced
late last evening Vivek you gave us a
heads up that this Landmark deal is
likely to be announced and bang on yet
again so congratulations on that front
you go first tell us about Glenmark live
well good morning absolutely you know
just as we had uh indicated yesterday
that the nirma group was the front
runner to go ahead and pick up a
majority controlling stake in Glenmark
Life Sciences from Glenmark Pharma along
expected lines you know yesterday
evening this particular deals was
announced so promoter entity Glenmark
Pharma is selling 75 stake in the
company to nirma limited so nirma
limited will acquire 75 out of the total
82.84 percent stake that Landmark Pharma
holds in Glenmark Life Sciences now this
particular stake sale is being done at
615 rupees which is the marginal two
percent discount to yesterday's closing
price now nirma you know on the back of
this particular deal the open offer
limit has been triggered so nirma has
announced an open offer for acquiring
the remainder over 17 percent stake and
we open offer price in that 631 rupees a
share analysts say that this particular
deal values Landmark life science as
eight times F525 EV to ebitda along with
that some important developments you
know to track as far as Landmark life is
concerned given the fact that Landmark
life you know the key Supply to Landmark
Pharma as far as the API business is
concerned so you know they will continue
to procure apis from Landmark Life
Sciences for five failures and along
with that you know there are certain
Business Development agreements in
overseas for a specified period uh the
stock is already up 49 in 2023 and also
remember in the IPO that came in August
2021 you know the I the IPO actually
valued Landmark Life Sciences at close
to 720 rupees a share okay and kudos to
you for breaking that story bringing it
to us before everyone else thanks a lot
for that Vivek so nirma making that big
Pharma push right and Glenmark Pharma of
course will be using the deal proceeds
towards repayment of debt but acres here
to give us all that you know uh Glenmark
Pharma could be in focus for this
morning
thanks to that well yes it's definitely
a big positive which has come in for
Glenmark because they will be net cash
positive post this deal so uh Glenn
Saldana did hold a press conference last
evening a webinar where he did indicate
that the money which they are getting
over 5 600 odd craws all of it will go
into a repayment of debt or they will
really repay the gross debt on their
books which stood at around 4 347 crores
as of f523 so net net post tax they
should have around 500 crores of cash
left on their books which would make
them net cash positive in terms of a
company now remember that this has
actually been a big overhang for
Glenmark throughout the draw lost debt
on their books and that's the reason why
they haven't really got a premium when
it comes to uh valuations despite the
fact that the stock has run up around
um from its 52-week low so maybe a lot
of that ground has now been covered but
traditionally it's always been an
overhang which is now removed now just a
couple of more details no decision on
rewarding shareholders as yet it will
probably be taken by the board in the
future they will not look to divest any
further assets here on which is
important they have been divesting
assets uh on a continuous basis after
this they are not looking to divest any
further assets they will continue to
pursue out licensing deals there is no
change in the guidance for f524 where
Revenue growth is estimated at around 10
to 11 odd percent that's probably going
to come down uh simply because of this
business going away and margins 19 to 20
they expect a 525 to be a real kicker
for the company in terms of the benefits
of this deal nubama is written on it
they've said that Landmark life is not
vital to Glenmark pharma's growth the
path to profitability is unlikely to be
impacted the estimate a three percent
profit accretion in fy25 they retain
whole given ignos uncertainty and a
Target price of 8 30. so yes it is
important that the gross debt is removed
but remember that they do have the r d
arm uh which the street will now focus
on and how exactly will Glenmark fund
the r d assets that they have on their
books going forward is something that
the street will also look out for going
forward
okay all right take that thanks a lot
for that but let's hop across to Vivek
back again Vivek tell us some more
stocks you're tracking well good morning
you have quite a few stocks on the radar
on the back of news flow idea Forge you
know the company has received orders
worth over 58 crores from the ministry
of Defense now this is to Supply close
to 400 surveillance copters along with
their accessories the next talk is rvnl
you know one order win coming in the
company along with its JV partner you
know has signed an mou with nhi this is
for construction of a sick Lane
Greenfield uh you know Varanasi Ranchi
Kolkata Highway the total project cost
is over
1270 crore with RV and L share in the JV
being 49 and lastly nbcc2 on our radar
the company has received an award worth
over 100 crores from sale and this order
is for development work at township as
well as mines of sale Billy plant
okay thank you very much for that for
more stocks in the news we'll be joined
in serbi thanks so much for that so
first moving on first one on my radar is
Suntec Realty now the company partners
with IFC to create a joint platform
where they'll invest a total of 750
crores 330 crores will be invested by
IFC and the remaining 420 by Suntec
Realty now this platform is going to
expand the green Urban housing in
Maharashtra where they will promote
development of 12 000 housing units
across four to six green housing
projects in Mumbai next is ICICI Lombard
bhargav Das Gupta tenders resignation as
MD and CEO of the company to pursue
opportunities outside of India now he
has served the country for uh serve the
company for 14 years and his his term
was anyway ending in April of 2024 so
this is seven months ahead of uh his
term ending so this was anticipated it'd
be slight negative for the company icsa
Securities sebi has issued an
administrative warning to the company
this warning is in connection with the
inspection of books and records with
related to The Merchant banking
activities they have also initiated
other quasi judicial proceedings in this
connection itself but as of now there is
no Financial impact to the company but
it'll still be negative
thank you very much for that and let me
end it with Wipro where the CFO of the
company jatin Dalal has stepped down uh
he's been the CFO of the company since
2015 so close to about eight years and
aparna Ayer who's been a part of the
finance team will be taking his place as
the new CFO of the company but you know
it's not just one exit for a Wipro Wipro
has seen a Spate of senior level exits
in the last one year and I can count
more than you know close to about 10 of
them and some of them have gone on to
take on CEO position and other companies
so there was to be someone called angan
guha who's now become the CEO of birla
soft and the list goes on and these are
all the exits that you can see just in
the last one year so and CFO stepping
down you know could add that additional
overhang on Wipro today absolutely and I
think in the last if you map the last
five six years Wipro has always
underperformed its peers right this
could maybe be one of the reasons I mean
a string of exits in the last couple of
years is definitely gone well at all
they've got a new CEO a couple of years
back Theory teleport so you know he did
reorganize the company made some changes
so new people came in some of the old
guard decided to step out and pursue you
know other opportunities but Wipro
respect as a turnaround story it did
very well in the covered years when
there was this big rush of you know
transformation but since then the growth
rates for the company have faltered uh
again so that turnaround hasn't really
played right now the only thing that
works for Wipro is you know the cash
balance Etc and also its valuations are
cheaper than the rest of this just one
point to add you know with regard to the
exits Mr Goa as you said he joined
biddler stuff and everyone said it's
doomsday for uh biddlers of when when Mr
DK he left because he had that big
vision and the stock opened up around
six seven percent and from there I think
it's up close around 50 yeah post Mr Gua
joining uh coming on board on bidla surf
okay well let's see what happens with
Wipro today but plenty of stocks in
focus in case you missed out on any of
them stocks with positive news flow
there's Glenmark Pharma Banks idea Forge
Tech rdnl nbcc Suntec Realty while
stocks with negative news flow there's
Landmark Life Sciences before Lombard
and ICICI Securities but there's also a
lot happening in the world of
Commodities Brentwood continues to be
around 93 94 a barrel so that is a bit
of a headwind for our markets Manisha is
here to give us the latest on that
Manisha good morning
morning and thank you for that Sonia
well even with the gain that we are
seeing come back on Friday the crude is
still headed for a weekly decline down
by nearly a postage point after gaining
10 in last three weeks I mean a lot
could change within the Europe and U.S
time zones right now uh the latest
trigger for the game that you're seeing
right now comes in after Russia is
banned fuel exposed to ex-soviet states
to ensure that there is stability in
crisis within the country and that's uh
supported the prices in any case we've
seen U.S inventories decline uh the U.S
oil output is also expected to decline
for a third straight month in the month
of October and then we all are working
with the fourth quarter deficit
estimates in any case so the crude oil
prices one is back above 90 there is
definite pressure that we have seen in
the metal prices uh nearly two percent
of decline overnight so with that copper
is now trading at a five-week close
nickel at a 14-month close the strength
in U.S dollar higher inventories all of
that seems to be pushing it down
okay Manisha thank you very much for
that get into a short break up next upon
method of Elixir equities will join in
for a fundamental stock analysis later
on we'll also connect with b-presser now
icsa bank and Lakshmi Ayer of kotak
alternate asset manager to discuss all
about JP Morgan's uh you know plan to
include the Indian Bonds in the emerging
market index stay tuned
[Music]
foreign